/* global define */
define(function(require, exports, module) {

	module.exports = {
		displayName: 'JLPT N5 Verbs',
		items: [{ front: 'to meet', back: 'あう' },
				{ front: 'to open', back: 'あく' },
				{ front: 'to open', back: 'あける' },
				{ front: 'to give', back: 'あげる' },
				{ front: 'to play', back: 'あそぶ' },
				{ front: 'to take a shower', back: 'あびる' },
				{ front: 'to wash', back: 'あらう' },
				{ front: 'to be, to exist', back: 'ある' },
				{ front: 'to possess', back: 'ある' },
				{ front: 'to walk', back: 'あるく' },
				{ front: 'to say, to tell', back: 'いう' },
				{ front: 'to go', back: 'いく' },
				{ front: 'need, must haven be required', back: 'いる' },
				{ front: 'to exist', back: 'いる' },
				{ front: 'to insert, to put in', back: 'いれる' },
				{ front: 'to sing', back: 'うたう' },
				{ front: 'to be born', back: 'うまれる' },
				{ front: 'to sell', back: 'うる' },
				{ front: 'to get up, to stand up', back: 'おきる' },
				{ front: 'to put', back: 'おく' },
				{ front: 'to send', back: 'おくる' },
				{ front: 'to push', back: 'おす' },
				{ front: 'to memorize, to remember', back: 'おぼえる' },
				{ front: 'to swim', back: 'およぐ' },
				{ front: 'to get off', back: 'おりる' },
				{ front: 'to end', back: 'おわる' },
				{ front: 'to buy', back: 'かう' },
				{ front: 'to return an object', back: 'かえす' },
				{ front: 'to return home', back: 'かえる' },
				{ front: 'to take time or money', back: 'かかる' },
				{ front: 'to write', back: 'かく' },
				{ front: 'to wear', back: 'かける' },
				{ front: 'to make a phone call', back: 'かける' },
				{ front: 'to lend', back: 'かす' },
				{ front: 'to put on a hat', back: 'かぶる' },
				{ front: 'to borrow', back: 'かりる' },
				{ front: 'to go out, to vanish', back: 'きえる' },
				{ front: 'to listen', back: 'きく' },
				{ front: 'to cut', back: 'きる' },
				{ front: 'to wear, to put on', back: 'きる' },
				{ front: 'to come', back: 'くる' },
				{ front: 'to turn off, to switch off', back: 'けす' },
				{ front: 'to answer', back: 'こたえる' },
				{ front: 'to be in trouble', back: 'こまる' },
				{ front: 'to blossom', back: 'さく' },
				{ front: 'to open an umbrella', back: 'さす' },
				{ front: ' to die, to pass away', back: 'しぬ' },
				{ front: 'to close', back: 'しまる' },
				{ front: 'to close', back: 'しめる' },
				{ front: 'to fasten a belt', back: 'しめる' },
				{ front: 'to know', back: 'しる' },
				{ front: 'to breath, to smoke', back: 'すう' },
				{ front: 'to live, to reside somewhere', back: 'すむ' },
				{ front: 'to do', back: 'する' },
				{ front: 'to sit', back: 'すわる' },
				{ front: 'to take out, hand in', back: 'だす' },
				{ front: 'to stand', back: 'たつ' },
				{ front: 'to ask, to request', back: 'たのむ' },
				{ front: 'to eat', back: 'たべる' },
				{ front: 'to be different', back: 'ちがう' },
				{ front: 'to use', back: 'つかう' },
				{ front: 'to get tired', back: 'つかれる' },
				{ front: 'to arrive', back: 'つく' },
				{ front: 'to make, to produce', back: 'つくる' },
				{ front: 'to turn on', back: 'つける' },
				{ front: 'to work for someone', back: 'つとめる' },
				{ front: 'to go out', back: 'でかける' },
				{ front: 'can do', back: 'できる' },
				{ front: 'to leave', back: 'でる' },
				{ front: 'to fly', back: 'とぶ' },
				{ front: 'to stop', back: 'とまる' },
				{ front: ' to take', back: 'とる' },
				{ front: 'to take a photo', back: 'とる' },
				{ front: 'to sing, mew, moo', back: 'なく' },
				{ front: 'to form a line', back: 'ならぶ' },
				{ front: 'to line up', back: 'ならべる' },
				{ front: 'to become', back: 'なる' },
				{ front: 'to take off clothes', back: 'ぬぐ' },
				{ front: 'to sleep', back: 'ねる' },
				{ front: 'to climb up', back: 'のぼる' },
				{ front: 'to drink', back: 'のむ' },
				{ front: 'to take, to ride', back: 'のる' },
				{ front: 'to enter', back: 'はいる' },
				{ front: 'to put on shoes', back: 'はく' },
				{ front: 'to begin, to start', back: 'はじまる' },
				{ front: 'to run', back: 'はしる' },
				{ front: 'to work', back: 'はたらく' },
				{ front: 'to talk, to speak, to tell', back: 'はなす' },
				{ front: 'to put something on, to stick', back: 'はる' },
				{ front: 'to clear up', back: 'はれる' },
				{ front: 'to pull', back: 'ひく' },
				{ front: 'to play an instrument', back: 'ひく' },
				{ front: 'to blow (wind)', back: 'ふく' },
				{ front: 'to fall (rain, snow)', back: 'ふる' },
				{ front: 'to turn', back: 'まがる' },
				{ front: 'to wait', back: 'まつ' },
				{ front: 'to polish, to brush', back: 'みがく' },
				{ front: 'to show', back: 'みせる' },
				{ front: 'to see, to watch', back: 'みる' },
				{ front: 'to have, to own', back: 'もつ' },
				{ front: 'to rest', back: 'やすむ' },
				{ front: ' to do', back: 'やる' },
				{ front: 'to call', back: 'よぶ' },
				{ front: 'to read', back: 'よむ' },
				{ front: 'to know, to understand', back: 'わかる' },
				{ front: 'to forget', back: 'わすれる' },
				{ front: 'to hand over', back: 'わたす' },
				{ front: 'to cross', back: 'わたる' }]
	};
})